Jacob Johnson

Administration - Claims Legal Assistant

Hardworking Claims Legal Assistant bringing administrative and legal support expertise with strong writing skills and work ethic. Currently attending a Full Stack Web Development coding boot camp at UT Austin and as a result, capable of working on the back-end and front-end of applications.

Work History

2019-07 -

Administrative Claims Legal Assistant

Current

Progressive Auto Insurance, Austin, Texas

- Worked alongside attorneys, paralegals, and fellow administrative assistants on complex cases and legal processes.
- Provided PowerPoints for attorneys to use in meetings for internal training purposes.
- Created Month End reports to manage new cases, ongoing cases, and closed cases for attorneys.
- Created training docs on company processes for use by fellow assistants and paralegals.
- Referred cases to outside counsel, providing file materials to form defense to protect Progressive in suits and subpoenas.

2013-02 -2019-07

Administration Upload Specialist

Mood Media, Austin, Texas

- Used APIs in tandem with Oracle software to mass update our customers' service contracts and account information.
- Worked directly with Premier Service Managers to recontract customers or update their current terms per updated contracts.
- Used Microsoft Excel on a daily basis to make mass changes such as recurring monthly revenue, net terms, or addresses to hundreds of locations in a single upload to Oracle.

Education

2008-08 -

Bachelor of Arts: English

2022-12

Texas State University - San Marcos, TX

- Majored in English
- Minored in Film

2021-07 -

Full Stack Web Developer

Current

University of Texas At Austin - Austin, TX

Interests

Co-Host of Horror Movie Podcast 'Jacob & Rhys vs. Evil'

Movie and Video Game Reviews On Screenpunk.net

Contact

Address

Austin, TX, 78744

Phone

(512) 586-0027

E-mail

jljohnson1454@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jacobjohnson-53256365

Skills

HTML, CSS, Javascript

Web, Third-Party, and Server-Side APIs

Node.js, Express.js, SQL, OOP, ORM, and MVC

Adobe Creative Suite

Podcast Software/Recording Experience